diabetes-health.net 2014-06-25

# Diabetes Health - Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is a top priority at Diabetes Health. We've taken precautions to secure your information and our physical premises. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the [Webmaster](mailto:webmaster@diabeteshealth.com). 

Diabetes Health uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information.

**Site Feedback**

Under "[Contact Us](https://diabeteshealth.com/company/contact-us.html)," we maintain e-mail links to various Diabetes Health members to collect feedback on products and services. We collect visitors' contact information (like e-mail address). Customer contact information is used only to respond to inquiries.

**Editorial Polls**

We collect personal information from our occasional editorial polls for citation purposes in the print magazine and/or website. If you do not wish your information to be published, please check the appropriate box to have your information withheld.

**E-mail List**

If you choose to receive our weekly newsletter, we ask for an e-mail address you would like Diabetes Health sent to. We do not sell your e-mail address. Customer contact information is used to contact visitors when necessary. To opt out of receiving future mailings, click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all our newsletters.

**Online Surveys**

Occasionally we send out an online survey via e-mail to random newsletter subscribers. Our surveys ask visitors for contact information (e-mail address) and general demographic data (such as gender, geographic location or occupation). We use survey results on an aggregate basis to improve Diabetes Health. No personal information is shared with third parties. We do not sell your e-mail address to marketers.

**Ad Serving**

We use a third-party software to serve ads. Diabetes Health may use information (but not your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about visits to our site, in combination with non-personally identifiable information about your purchases and interests from other sources, in order to provide ads about goods and services of interest to you.

In addition, we share site usage information with other companies for the sole purpose of managing and targeting ads and for market research. Diabetes Health and third-party ad servers may occasionally track pages you visit through with pixel tags (or "clear gifs"). In the course of serving ads, an advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your computer.

**Risk Assessment**

If you agree to link your Google Health Account to retrieve medical data, we will use this data to populate fields in the Risk Assessment form.

If you agree to link your Google Health Account with your Diabetes Health account, our personalized service will send you notices relevant to your medical history, including clinical trials, surveys, TV interviews, medical product information, and links to our free digital magazine. These notices will be sent out on an average of once every two months.

We will not store specific data from your Google Health profile; we will only maintain a link (session token) between the two services. You can choose to unlink your Google Health Account with your Diabetes Health account and we will retain no information about the link.

If you are not logged in to your Diabetes Health account and you retrieve information from Google Health, we will store no information related to the link after the assessment.

If you do not link a Google Health Account when using the form, no information about your answers or diagnosis will be retained after the form has been processed.

We will not sell individual or aggregate user data collected from Google Health. We will not disclose your information to third parties without your explicit consent, unless required by law. We will not target advertisements to users who link their Google Health Accounts with their Diabetes Health accounts.

**Contacting Diabetes Health**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, contact:

**Diabetes Health**  
365 Bel Marin Keys Blvd, Suite 100  
Novato, CA 94949

Tel: (415) 883-1990  
Fax: (415) 883-1932

Or use the [Contact Us](https://diabeteshealth.com/company/contact-us.html) page
